bangkok925.com 2018-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Privacy Policy

We are well aware of your confidence in its services and security related to your personal information. We take great care in this regard to avoid any scam. By visiting our website, you agree to the following privacy notice.

�

**What personal information is required by the site?**

The personal information given by you help us improve the services provided by us and make it more personalized.

**Information provided by the visitors �**

Any information given by you is received and stored by us for various future usage like contacting you regarding your order, customizing your shopping preferences and responding to your queries etc. You may opt not to provide certain information if you wish so, but it may keep you from availing our certain special features.

�

**Automatic Information**

Whenever you interact with our website, we request you to fill some information and store it for future interaction with you. We too use �cookies� to track certain information when you access our website.

Our website sometimes collects your internet protocol (IP) address for security purposes. This is done to make sure that you are the real buyer and to avoid anyone else making purchases using your name and credit card.

�

**E-mail Communication**

We keep you informed and updated of our new arrivals and policies through emails by sending order confirmation, newsletters and new product updates etc. You have a choice to opt for only order related emails to be sent to you if you wish so.

�

**Cookies! What are they?**

�

Cookies are the text files, used for identification of your web browser as well as for other storage features. These files are transferred to your computer through the web browser for the purpose of identification.

�

**Your information is secured**

�

We respect your privacy and under no circumstances share with others unless it is required for the transaction completion purpose for your order. Our secure Sockets Layer(SSL) software helps in keeping the information given by you by encrypting it. No one can see your credit card number since only last five digits are shown in your order. The complete number is only given to the concerned credit card company for transaction processing.

�

We would like to advise you too to be careful regarding your personal credit card information and always signoff when you complete your order.�

You can access your account and see the record of your interaction with us.

�

**Terms of Use and Notices**

On visiting our website, any of your concern regarding privacy is subject to our notice and conditions of use. This includes any kind of dispute, limitations on damages and application of the local law. Please �contact us� if you have any query or dispute. We will look into the matter and try to solve it as long as possible.�

Our privacy policy if applicable for all the information that we have about you and we standby our promise of keeping your information secured. We keep you informed regarding any changes in our privacy policy and conditions through emails and newsletters, unless you opt for not to get these reminders. Our website is also updated regularly and you can see the latest information and additions there by visiting it more frequently.�

�

**What information you need to provide**

You are requested to provide some specific information when you brows our website for placing your order, or want to post a review or some query etc. This information includes filling in your name, address, age, sex, email id and phone number etc. We require your credit card number too when you buy products from us using online payment option.

�

**Queries�**

If you have any queries regarding our privacy policy or want to get more information, kindly contact our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us " link in the side menu.

�
